## **Sharon M Tan**

Linkedin.com/in/sharonmt

### **EXECUTIVE SUMMARY**

My life as a journalist, writer and editor of more than 20 years, has helped me hone systems thinking, active listening and clear communication skills. In the current age of cloud technology, I am inspired to discover ways to infuse new skills and solutions into my strong base of experience. Every problem has a story, and the solution often lies within. My strength is getting to the heart of every story. Curious, collaborative, and adventurous; I see opportunities, rather than problems. I prefer to ask and listen, rather than show and tell. I like to try out, instead of sit back. Allow me to facilitate impactful conversations that result in collaborative solutions.

\_\_\_\_\_\_

#### **CURRENT**

**DevOps Engineer** May 2022 - present

Olea (Singapore)

- System administration of Olea platforms (Fintech)
- · CI/CD, Automation, Configuration Management, Database
- AWS, GitHub, Jira, ArgoCD, FreshService

### **EXPERIENCE**

 DevOps Analyst
 Oct 2021
 - Jun 2022

 Lexly (Singapore)
 Jul 1999
 - Jul 2000

- DevOps Lead; SGUP-CT Microsoft Cloud Support & DevOps programme
- CI/CD, Database Management; AWS, GitLab, Docker

# Web Manager

Intel (Singapore) Jul 1999 - Jul 2000

Manage internal website and channel to serve Intel's business customers

### Journalist (web content)

Singapore Press Holdings (SPH)

May 1995 - Jun 1999

- Manage delivery of digital content
- · Create multimedia stories and features

## **SKILLS**

Cloud: AWS, Azure; Scripting: YAML, Python; Tools: GitLab, Docker, Ansible, Terraform

## **ADDITIONAL SKILLS & CERTIFICATIONS**

Microsoft Azure Fundamentals (AZ900)	2021
Advanced Certificate in Training & Assessment – IAL (ACTA; now ACLP)	2017
Taiji teacher/ instructor – World Nam Wah Taiji Gong Association	2007 - present

### **EDUCATION**

SGUP-CT Cloud Support & DevOps	2021	-	2022
--------------------------------	------	---	------

Generation (Singapore)

Bachelor of Arts (Communications) 1990 - 1994

Trinity Western University (British Columbia, Canada)